# Kevin J. Song

Web Developer | Software Engineer

707 Baltusrol Rd. Aberdeen, MD 21001

www.kevsong.com

 $\boxtimes$ 

kevinmnm2010@gmail.com

301-802-8670

## **PROFILE**

Reliable, energetic, and passionate web developer. Strong frontend and backend knowledge. Strong JavaScript knowledge with over a year and a half of practical experience. Acquired Secret Interim Clearance as of 06/13/2021. Acquired CompTIA Security+ certification.

#### **SKILL**

HTML | (S)CSS | JavaScript | jQuery | Vue.js | Vuetify | React.js | Redux | Firebase | Node.js | Express.js | MongoDB | GIT | MySQL | Boostrap | UI/UX Design | AJAX | Webpack | ESLint | Prettier | SEO | Frontend | Backend | Full-Stack | Translation | Interpretation | Social Media Marketing | TEASOL/TEFL | CompTIA Security+

## **EXPERIENCE**

TELESIS Corp.

February, 2021 - Current

# Web Developer

Full-Stack Web Developer for United States Army. Responsible to develop & maintain i-JBCP application within public and secret level. Mainly work with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL, and PHP. Secret interim clearance was acquired as of 6/13/2021.

### Continuum Global Solutions, LLC

October, 2019 - February, 2021

# Team Lead & IT Support

IT Support agent. Troubleshoot/diagnose IT issues. CVS Specialty Pharmacy benefit verification duty. Responsibilities included but not limited to: Resolving team issues, conducting quality audits, team training, taking escalated (sup) calls, substituting supervisor when absent, assigning work, etc.

#### Upwork Global Inc.

August, 2019 - October, 2019

# **Translator & Interpreter**

Work as a freelancer on upwork.com platform. Korean/English translation and interpretation, Language voiceover talents, international market research, international medical survey, and Medicare/Medicaid translation.

#### Conduent Inc.

June, 2016 - July, 2019

#### Member Service Representative

Aetna Medicare Part C advantage plan member service representative. Responsibilities included member resolution, member/provider resolution, claims processing, appeal/grievance submission, and enrollment registry.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Business Administration**

2013 - 2018

Frostburg State University

General Management & Entrepreneurship

## **LANGUAGE**

English Korean